A Guide to the Melvin E. Steadman collection, 1698-1927
Library of Virginia
- Series I: Local records, 1755-1927., Extent: 10 boxes. (Box 1-10)
  - Maryland, Baltimore County Bonds, 1747. (Box 10, Folder 29, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1237)
    Bond of Thomas Sligh.
  - Maryland, Frederick County County Court, 1800-1802. (Box 10, Folder 30, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1237)
    John Burkhead vs. Benedict Lewes (1800)>
    Joseph Howard vs. Benjamin Hopkins (1800).
    William and Adam Michael vs. Baalis Coomes (1802).
  - Maryland, Frederick County Deed Book W, 1774. (Box 10, Folder 31, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1237)
    Deed between Aden Pencost and William Trammell.
  - Maryland, Frederick County Justice of the Peace Records, 1868. (Box 10, Folder 32, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1237)
    Certificate of Thomas Johnson.
  - Maryland, Prince George County Justice of the Peace Records, 1813. (Box 10, Folder 33, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1237)
    Commissions of William Marshall and William K. Clagett.
  - New York, Dutchess County Supreme Court, 1897. (Box 10, Folder 34, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1237)
    Methodist Episcopal Church in the center of Stanford vs. Sarah S. Hunting executors.
  - Texas, Grayson County District Court, 1894. (Box 10, Folder 35, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1237)
    Sarah A. Dove etc. vs. H. P. Howard etc.
  - Washington (D.C.) Marriage Records, 1921. (Box 10, Folder 36, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1237)
    Marriage license of Addison Householder and Lorena B. Wolford.
  - Washington (D.C.) Wills, 1899. (Box 10, Folder 37, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1237)
    Certificate stating Charles B. Purvis as executor for Frederick G. Barbadoes estate.
  - West Virginia, Berkley County, 1801. (Box 10, Folder 38)
    Oath of John Byers regarding Isaac Newland, son of John Newland.
  - West Virginia, Jefferson County County Court, 1809. (Box 10, Folder 38a, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1237)
    Summons in Ann Griffeth vs. William Harding.
    Jonah Thompson and Sons vs. William Harding Administrator.
    Charles Binns vs. William Harding Administrator.
- Series II: Organizational records, 1806-1926., Extent: 1/2 box. (Box 10)
  The Organizational records series include accounts, bills, certificates, deeds, list of trustees, policies, and receipts. Included are papers of the Alexandria Boarding School and Leesburg Academy, as well as records relating to the Methodist Episcopal Church in Alexandria, Falls Church, Fairfax, Lovettsville, Loudoun, and Sussex County. Of note are affidavits and certificates concerning a dispute and charges against Thacker Muire. Muire was known for instigating numerous lawsuits in his neighborhood and was later expelled from the Methodist Episcopal Church in Sussex County, Virginia.
  Arranged alphabetically by organizations name.
  - Alexandria Boarding School, 1842. (Box 10, Folder 39, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1237)
    Boarding and tuition receipt of Charles B. Tebbs.
  - Leesburg Academy (Loudoun Co.), 1806-1834. (Box 10, Folder 40, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1237)
    Includes bills for building of academy, deeds, Mutual Assurance Society policy, and newspaper clipping.
  - Loudoun Valley Academy (Loudoun Co.), 1870. (Box 10, Folder 41, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1237)
    Tuition receipt of Heston Hirst.
  - Methodist Episcopal Church (Alexandria), 1850-1890. (Box 10, Folder 42, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1237)
    Legal opinion regarding church by Henry Hunter Davis (1850) and Church appointment (1890).
  - Methodist Episcopal Church (Falls Church), 1926. (Box 10, Folder 43, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1237)
    Copy of Deed of Dedication of Crossman Methodist Episcopal Church.
  - Methodist Episcopal Church (Lovettsville), 1869-1870. (Box 10, Folder 44, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1237)
    Application and list of trustees.
  - Methodist Episcopal Church (Middleburg, Loudoun Co,), 1866-1867. (Box 10, Folder 45, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1237)
    Appointment and election of trustees.
  - Methodist Episcopal Church (Nelson Chapel, Fairfax Co.), 1882. (Box 10, Folder 46, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1237)
    Deed.
  - Methodist Episcopal Church (Sussex Co.), 1822-1830. (Box 10, Folder 47, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1237)
    Affidavits and certificates concerning dispute and charges against Thacker Muire, who was later expelled from the church.
  - Methodist Episcopal Church (Fairfax Co.), 1842. (Box 10, Folder 48-49, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1237)
    Testimony, petitions, correspondence and other papers regarding the case against Rev. Charles A. Davis. Rev. Davis was charged with attacking a fellow parishioner.
  - Mutual Assurance Society of Virginia, 1825. (Box 10, Folder 50, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1237)
    Policy for William Paxson (Waterford, Va.).
  - U. S. Naval Department, nd. (Box 10, Folder 51, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1237)
    Blank form for application for prize money person out of service.
  - U.S. Patent Office, 1846. (Box 10, Folder 52, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1237)
    Assignment of right in a patent to William Palmer.
- Series III: Personal papers, 1806-1926., Extent: 5 boxes. (Box 11-15)
  The Private Papers series contains accounts, agreements, correspondence, deeds, estate accounts and inventories, receipts, and wills. The bulk of the collection consists of estate accounts and inventories. Surnames mentioned include: Binns, Chichester, Cooke, Davis, Ellzey, Hamilton, Hopkins, Lane, Lewis, McCabe, Mason, Oxley, Price, Scott, Sinclair, Taylor, Updike, Whaley, and Wrenn, among others.
  Arranged alphabetically by peronal name, with miscellaneous materials arranged to the front.
  - Miscellaneous accounts, 1754-1875. (Box 11, Folder 1, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1237)
  - Miscellaneous bonds, 1757-1888. (Box 11, Folder 2, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1237)
  - Miscellaneous envelopes, 1757-1888. (Box 11, Folder 2a)
  - Miscellaneous estate accounts, 1773-1866. (Box 11, Folder 3, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1237)
  - Miscellaneous receipts, 1795-1865. (Box 11, Folder 4, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1237)
  - Alexander, John, 1796-1799. (Box 11, Folder 5, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1238)
    Accounts.
  - Alexander family, 1793-1796. (Box 11, Folder 6, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1238)
    Alexander vs. Alexander.
  - Ashford, Michael, 1799. (Box 11, Folder 7, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1238)
    Correspondence to Francis Berryman.
  - Barnes family, 1755. (Box 11, Folder 8, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1238)
    Account.
  - Beans, Samuel, 1853. (Box 11, Folder 9, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1238)
    Tuition receipt.
  - Bennett, E.L., 1892-1893. (Box 11, Folder 10, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1238)
    Correspondence.
  - Binns, John A., Rev., 1791-1833. (Box 11, Folder 11-12, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1238)
    Estate accounts and inventory.
  - Binns, John A., Esq., 1833. (Box 11, Folder 13, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1238)
    Correspondence from Noble S. Braden.
  - Binns, Simon A., 1819-1832. (Box 11, Folder 14, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1238)
    Estate accounts.
  - Brick, Almond, 1865. (Box 11, Folder 15, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1238)
  - Broadwater, Charles, 1757-1834. (Box 11, Folder 16, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1238)
    Accounts and receipts.
  - Brooke, Hannah, 1776-1790. (Box 11, Folder 17, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1238)
  - Brown, Nathaniel, 1752. (Box 11, Folder 18, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1238)
    Depositions of John and William Brown and William Price.
  - Canby & Hough, 1785. (Box 11, Folder 19, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1238)
    Correspondence to John Sutton.
  - Carnan, William, 1772-1779. (Box 11, Folder 20, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1238)
  - Carter Brothers Mill (Loudoun Co.), 1874-1876. (Box 11, Folder 21, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1238)
  - Chichester, George M., 1823. (Box 11, Folder 22, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1238)
    Correspondence to Chichester regarding the health of William Cooke and a disease in St. Francisville, Louisiana, that killed many slaves in the area.
  - Chichester, Marguerite, 1868. (Box 11, Folder 23, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1238)
    correspondence.
  - Chick, William, 1800-1803. (Box 11, Folder 24, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1238)
  - Chilton, Sarah, 1787-1788. (Box 11, Folder 25, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1238)
  - Chinn, Richard, 1796-1802. (Box 11, Folder 26, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1238)
  - Church, Merton E., 1898. (Box 11, Folder 27, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1238)
    Correspondence from Albert F. Fox.
  - Claggett, Thomas, 1788-1796. (Box 12, Folder 1, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1239)
  - Claypoole, Joseph, 1768-1786. (Box 12, Folder 2, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1239)
  - Cooke family, 1739-1827. (Box 12, Folder 3-4, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1239)
    Papers including correspondence, plats, and deeds (many from Thomas Lord Fairfax). Also includes the wills of William Cocke, John Graham, and Elizabeth Graham, and papers from case Graham vs. Graham.
  - Coleman, Richard, nd. (Box 12, Folder 5, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1239)
  - Combs, Joseph, 1803-1805. (Box 12, Folder 6, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1239)
  - Conn, Garrard Trammell, 1773. (Box 12, Folder 7, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1239)
    Accounts and correspondence.
  - Connard, William, 1772-1783. (Box 12, Folder 8, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1239)
  - Crawford, B., 1847. (Box 12, Folder 9, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1239)
    Receipts.
  - Darne family, 1809-1857. (Box 12, Folder 10, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1239)
    Estate accounts, inventory, and correspondence of Amelia Darne and Nicholas Darne (will).
  - Davis and Bro. (Bristoe, Va.), 1880. (Box 12, Folder 11, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1239)
  - Davis, David, 1786. (Box 12, Folder 12, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1239)
    Release of bound servant by James Barnes.
  - Davis, Matthew, 1861-1866. (Box 12, Folder 13, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1239)
  - Deming, William H., 1840-1854. (Box 12, Folder 14, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1239)
  - Dickins, Margaret Harvie Randolph, nd. (Box 12, Folder 15, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1239)
    Correspondence to Mrs. Dickins, Ossian Hall, from A. M. Fitzhugh.
  - Dougherty, James, 1780-1790. (Box 12, Folder 16, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1240)
    School accounts.
  - Dougherty, Patrick, 1792-1796. (Box 12, Folder 17, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1240)
    Receipts and warrant.
  - Douglas, James Walker, 1794. (Box 12, Folder 18, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1240)
  - Duncan, Benjamin, 1820-1822. (Box 12, Folder 19, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1240)
    Accounts and receipts. Also includes agreements for Duncan to teach in Cameron Parish, Loudoun Co.
  - Elzey family, 1784-1808. (Box 12, Folder 20, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1240)
    Estate inventory of Thomas Elzey, will of Jane Gregg, and accounts and depositions of Lewis Elzey and William Elzey.
  - Fairfax, George William, 1811. (Box 12, Folder 21, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1240)
    Copy of will (1787).
  - Fields, Thomas, 1755-1759. (Box 12, Folder 22, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1240)
  - Fletcher, Abraham, 1760-1761. (Box 12, Folder 23, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1240)
  - Fox, Gabriel, 1771. (Box 12, Folder 24, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1240)
  - Fox, James, 1803. (Box 12, Folder 25, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1240)
    Advertisement for the estate of James Fox.
  - Garrison, Nehemiah, 1759-1784. (Box 12, Folder 26, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1240)
    Accounts and bonds.
  - Gray, John, 1836. (Box 12, Folder 27, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1240)
    Correspondence to Charles Binns.
  - Green, John M., 1813. (Box 12, Folder 28, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1240)
    Correspondence to Rawleigh Chinn.
  - Hains, Daniel, 1815. (Box 12, Folder 29, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1240)
    Bond and account for stilling liquor in Loudoun Co.
  - Hamilton, Robert, 1765-1803. (Box 12, Folder 30-32, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1240)
    Accounts, receipts, estate inventory, and will.
  - Hamilton, James, 1760-1800. (Box 12, Folder 33, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1240)
  - Hampton, William H., 1816-1822. (Box 12, Folder 34, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1240)
  - Hancock, William, 1818. (Box 12, Folder 35, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1240)
    Correspondence to Charles Binns, Leesburg.
  - Harden, Joal [Joel?], 1809. (Box 12, Folder 36, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1240)
  - Harding, William H., 1797-1809. (Box 12, Folder 37, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1241)
  - Harrison, B. W., 1835. (Box 12, Folder 38, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1241)
    Correspondence from J. R. Cooke.
  - Hereford, John, 1761-1790. (Box 12, Folder 39, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1241)
  - Hirst, Hector, 1867-1876. (Box 12, Folder 40, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1241)
  - Holifield family, 1759. (Box 13, Folder 1, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1241)
    West vs. Holifield and Moxley vs. Holifield.
  - Holmes, William, 1766-1830. (Box 13, Folder 2, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1241)
  - Hopkins, Benjamin, 1800-1802. (Box 13, Folder 3, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1241)
  - Hoskins, William, 1811-1816. (Box 13, Folder 4, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1241)
  - Hughes, John H., 1852. (Box 13, Folder 5, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1241)
  - Jones, Ann, 1801. (Box 13, Folder 6, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1241)
  - Kerrick, Stephen, 1805. (Box 13, Folder 7, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1241)
  - King, John, 1763-1791. (Box 13, Folder 8, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1241)
  - Koon, Eleanor M., 1896-1897. (Box 13, Folder 9, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1241)
  - Lane, William Carr, 1764-1804. (Box 13, Folder 10, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1241)
    Estate accounts and inventory. (continues in next folder)
  - Lane family, 1772-1850. (Box 13, Folder 11, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1241)
    Estate accounts and inventories of Charles Lane and William Carr Lane.
  - Lawson, J., 1820. (Box 13, Folder 12, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1242)
    Correspondence to Sampson Blincoe, Leesburg.
  - Lay, Joseph, 1807-1809. (Box 13, Folder 13, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1242)
  - Leakin, Abraham, 1801. (Box 13, Folder 14, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1242)
  - Lease, John, 1794-1796. (Box 13, Folder 15, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1242)
  - Lee, Alexander D., 1862-1868. (Box 13, Folder 16, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1242)
  - Lee, George, 1857. (Box 13, Folder 17, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1242)
  - Lee, James, 1771. (Box 13, Folder 18, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1242)
    Teaching agreement between Thomas Owsley and James Lee.
  - Lewis, Joseph Jr., 1782-1819. (Box 13, Folder 19, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1242)
    Correspondence, insurance papers, accounts, and receipts.
  - Lewis, Stephen, 1752-1758. (Box 13, Folder 20, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1242)
  - Lewis, Thomas, 1783. (Box 13, Folder 21, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1242)
    Judgement against Thomas Lewis.
  - Littlejohn, John, 1833. (Box 13, Folder 22, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1242)
    Account with Charles Binns.
  - Garrett Littleton and Co., 1839. (Box 13, Folder 22a)
    Correspondence with Robert H. Miller, Alexandria, regarding an order for china, meats, butters, and other goods for a store at the Pot House, Loudoun County.
  - Love, Thomas R., 1843. (Box 13, Folder 23, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1242)
  - Lumley, John, 1755. (Box 13, Folder 24, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1242)
    Receipt to Lumley for teaching the children of Samuel Jenkins.
  - McCabe, Patrick Henry, 1842. (Box 13, Folder 25, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1242)
    Agreement and plat of McCabe's land in Loudoun Co.
  - McCabe, Henry, 1785-1810. (Box 13, Folder 26, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1242)
    Estate accounts, deeds, and inventory.
  - McCarty, Daniel, 1784. (Box 13, Folder 27, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1242)
    Correspondence and receipts.
  - McKim family, 1858. (Box 13, Folder 28, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1242)
    Call for depositions in a chancery suit Elisha McKim and Gabriel McKim against Heath etc.
  - McVeigh Co., 1840. (Box 13, Folder 29, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1242)
    Correspondence requesting their law services from T. Shreve.
  - Macome, Hector, 1772-1775. (Box 13, Folder 30, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1242)
  - Mansfield, John, 1805-1806. (Box 13, Folder 31, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1242)
  - Marbury, Leonard, 1762. (Box 13, Folder 32, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1242)
  - Mason, Abraham B.T., 1797-1798. (Box 13, Folder 33, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1242)
  - Mason, Armistead Thomson, 1816. (Box 13, Folder 34, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1242)
    Correspondence to George Rust.
  - Mason, Elizabeth, 1791. (Box 13, Folder 35, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1242)
  - Mason, John Thomson, nd. (Box 13, Folder 36, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1242)
  - Mason, Sarah, 1798. (Box 13, Folder 37, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1242)
  - Mason, Stephens Thomson, 1796, 1852. (Box 13, Folder 38-39, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1242)
    Copy of deed from James and Ruth Ball and a report of slaves from the estate of Mason.
  - Mason, Thomson, 1771-1775. (Box 13, Folder 40, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1242)
  - Matheson & Co., 1874. (Box 13, Folder 41, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1242)
    Correspondence to James W. Shelton.
  - Mercer, Charles Fenton, 1839. (Box 13, Folder 42, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1242)
    Charles F. Mercer vs. Nathan and Peter Skinner. Includes plats of land in Loudoun Co.
  - Merrick, Griffith, 1770-1772. (Box 13, Folder 43, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1242)
  - Merrifield, George A.L., 1874-1918. (Box 14, Folder 1, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1242)
    Correspondence and deeds.
  - Merrifield, George A.L., 1919-1922. (Box 14, Folder 2-3, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1243)
  - Mills, George, 1772-1774. (Box 14, Folder 4, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1243)
  - Mines, Kearsley, 1819. (Box 14, Folder 5, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1243)
  - Moore, Thomas, 1876. (Box 14, Folder 6, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1243)
  - Morgan, John, 1815. (Box 14, Folder 7, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1243)
  - Myers, Benjamin and Elizabeth, 1793-1798. (Box 14, Folder 8, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1243)
  - Neabisco Mills (Prince William Co.), 1860. (Box 14, Folder 9, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1243)
  - Neilson, William, 1790. (Box 14, Folder 10, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1243)
    William Neilson vs. Nicholas McKnight.
  - Nickols, David, 1823. (Box 14, Folder 11, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1243)
    Correspondence from John Nickols, Ohio.
  - Nisbett, James, 1765-1767. (Box 14, Folder 12, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1243)
  - Noland, Elizabeth, 1771. (Box 14, Folder 13, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1243)
  - Orr, John, 1787. (Box 14, Folder 14, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1243)
  - Oxley, Henry, 1791. (Box 14, Folder 15, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1243)
  - Oxley, Rachel, 1780-1793. (Box 14, Folder 16, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1243)
  - Padgett, Francis, 1795-1808. (Box 14, Folder 17, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1243)
  - Pearson, Simon, 1762. (Box 14, Folder 18, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1243)
    Deed between Simon Pearson, son and heir at law of Thoams Pearson, and Lewis Ellzey.
  - Pugh, Samuel, 1779-1789. (Box 14, Folder 19, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1243)
  - Peyton, Ann, 1787. (Box 14, Folder 20, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1243)
    Correspondence to Joseph Stephens.
  - Pike, Jonathan, 1773-1788. (Box 14, Folder 21, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1243)
  - Price, Thomas, 1785-1792. (Box 14, Folder 22, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1243)
  - Pursel, John, 1774-1775. (Box 14, Folder 23, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1243)
    Promissory notes and receipts.
  - Ramsay and Kirkpatrick, 1771. (Box 14, Folder 24, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1243)
    Account with Charles Muirhead.
  - Ridgely, H., 1771. (Box 14, Folder 25, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1243)
  - Rose, Benjamin F., 1843-1850. (Box 14, Folder 26, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1243)
  - Savage, W., 1778. (Box 14, Folder 27, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1243)
  - Scott, James, 1769. (Box 14, Folder 28, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1243)
    Correspondence to James Keith.
  - Scott family, 1834-1857. (Box 14, Folder 29, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1244)
    Accounts, receipts, and correspondence.
  - Shepherd, Charles, 1806-1813. (Box 14, Folder 30, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1244)
  - Simpson, William, nd. (Box 14, Folder 31, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1244)
    Plat in case of William Simpson vs. William Wilkinson.
  - Sinclair, Robert A., 1869-1882. (Box 15, Folder 1, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1244)
    Agreements, clippings, and correspondence.
  - Sinclair, John, 1786-1797. (Box 15, Folder 2, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1244)
  - Skinner, Cornelius, 1811-1816. (Box 15, Folder 3, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1244)
  - Smith, Nathan, 1780-1782. (Box 15, Folder 4, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1244)
  - Smoot, C.C., 1847. (Box 15, Folder 5, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1244)
  - Talbott, Ann, 1776-1787. (Box 15, Folder 6, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1244)
  - Talmadge, T. W., nd. (Box 15, Folder 7, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1244)
    Blank invalid claim for pension, filed by attorney.
  - Tarlton, Jeremiah, 1801-1802. (Box 15, Folder 8, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1244)
    Receipts regarding estate of Benjamin Hopkins.
  - Taylor, Mahlow K., 1830-1865. (Box 15, Folder 9, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1244)
    Estate accounts and inventory, including copy of the will Robert J. Taylor (d. 1840).
  - Taylor, Thomas, 1797-1808. (Box 15, Folder 10, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1244)
  - Taylor, William R., 1801-1802. (Box 15, Folder 11, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1244)
  - Thompson, Amos, 1803. (Box 15, Folder 12, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1244)
  - Thompson, Samuel, 1790-1801. (Box 15, Folder 13, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1245)
  - Todhunter, John, 1772-1786. (Box 15, Folder 14, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1245)
  - Trammell, John, 1757-1766. (Box 15, Folder 15, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1245)
  - Trammell, Tabitha, 1847-1849. (Box 15, Folder 16, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1245)
  - Trone, John S., 1852. (Box 15, Folder 17, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1245)
    Agreement between Trone and Macrae.
  - Turley family, 1755-1853. (Box 15, Folder 18, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1245)
    Accounts, receipts, and promissory notes.
  - Tutt, Charles P., 1823-1835. (Box 15, Folder 19, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1245)
  - Tyler, William, 1837. (Box 15, Folder 20, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1245)
    William Tyler vs. Thomas Parker, Frederick County Chancery suit.
  - Updike, John, 1798-1802. (Box 15, Folder 21, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1245)
    Estate acounts and inventory.
  - Wade, Zephiniah, 1789-1798. (Box 15, Folder 22, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1245)
  - Warner, Peter, 1803. (Box 15, Folder 23, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1245)
  - West, George, 1759-1775. (Box 15, Folder 24, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1245)
  - Whaley, James, 1756-1783. (Box 15, Folder 25, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1245)
  - Wilson, Susanna, 1869. (Box 15, Folder 26, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1245)
    Estate account.
  - Winsell, Adam and Elizabeth, 1772-1774. (Box 15, Folder 27, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1245)
  - Woolard, William, 1787-1788. (Box 15, Folder 28, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1245)
  - Wrenn, William H., 1818-1854. (Box 15, Folder 29, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1246)
    Accounts, correspondence, and receipts.
  - Wrenn family, 1816-1876. (Box 15, Folder 30, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1246)
    Account book, accounts, promissory notes, and receipts.
  - Wright, R. L., 1857. (Box 15, Folder 31, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1246)
    Receipts for teaching students.
  - Maryland, Baltimore County Deeds [Oversize], 1834. (Box 16, Folder 1, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1246)
    Deed between George Howard and Benjamine Howard, etc.
  - Maryland, Baltimore County Deeds [Oversize], 1849. (Box 16, Folder 2, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1246)
    Deed between Louis Lurpenteur and George Arnold.
  - Loudoun County Plats and Surveys [Oversize], 1792, 1870. (Box 16, Folder 3, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1246)
    Survey for Thomas Neal estate (1792)
    Survey for Sydney L. Dodgson (1870).
  - Loudoun County Deeds [Oversize], 1761. (Box 16, Folder 4, Reel Miscellaneous Reel 1246)
    Deed between Lord Fairfax and J. Palmer.
  - County Deeds [Oversize]. (Box 17-19)
    Oversize deeds pulled from Local records. Separation notices placed in files where items pulled.